<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hello, World. on A. Michael Tatum</title><link>https://michaeltatum.xyz/</link><description>Recent content in Hello, World. on A. Michael Tatum</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>© 2025 Amaad Michael Tatum</copyright><atom:link href="https://michaeltatum.xyz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>AFK: Away From Keyboard 🥁⚽</title><link>https://michaeltatum.xyz/afk/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://michaeltatum.xyz/afk/</guid><description>A little bit about me when I&amp;rsquo;m logged off:
🥁 High-School Drumline 🥁 College Drumming 🥁 College Original Music ⚽ High-School Soccer</description></item><item><title>Drop me a line!</title><link>https://michaeltatum.xyz/contact/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://michaeltatum.xyz/contact/</guid><description>Feel free to reach out to me through any of the following methods:
Email You can email me at amaad.michael@gmail.com.
Social Media LinkedIn: A. Michael Tatum GitHub: amaad-michael Instagram: amaad_michael Location I am based slightly north of the Austin, TX metro area.</description></item><item><title>Greetings!</title><link>https://michaeltatum.xyz/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://michaeltatum.xyz/about/</guid><description>I am a Cloud Linux Engineer based right outside the Austin metro area, adept at managing complex infrastructure. I orchestrate servers across both Debian and RHEL distributions. I audit and enhance system security using tools like Kali and BlackArch to ensure a robust security posture. I focus on cloud platforms, system hardening, automation, and Infrastructure-as-Code, aimed at optimizing performance and reliability. I write technical papers and documentation, clearly articulating complex technical concepts.</description></item><item><title>Resume / CV</title><link>https://michaeltatum.xyz/resume/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://michaeltatum.xyz/resume/</guid><description>Your browser does not support embedding PDFs directly. You can download the resume here.</description></item><item><title>Certifications</title><link>https://michaeltatum.xyz/certs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://michaeltatum.xyz/certs/</guid><description>AZ-900: Azure Fundamentals Issuing Organization: Microsoft Date of Completion: September 2024 Verify AZ-900 Credential
Linux/UNIX Server Administrator Certificate Issuing Organization: Gwinnett Technical College Date of Completion: May 2012 PC Repair and Network Technician Certificate Issuing Organization: Gwinnett Technical College Date of Completion: May 2011</description></item><item><title>SiftDNS - DNS Privacy Service</title><link>https://michaeltatum.xyz/siftdns/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://michaeltatum.xyz/siftdns/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>